<helpText language="En_US">
	<helpGroup
		description="Fields shown when a user creates a new database (aka'dataspace') within a project">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_DatabaseName</helpId>
			<title>Database name</title>
			<text>The database name you choose can only contain alphabetic and
				numeric characters, i.e. a..z, 0..9, and cannot contain spaces.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_DataSources</helpId>
			<title>Data sources</title>
			<text>This field can be used to record where the data in the dataset
				came from. This might include details of print material that has
				been digitized, or of multiple sources that have been combined to
				produce the current dataset. (If not applicable, enter N/A.)
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_DataGathering</helpId>
			<title>Data gathering process</title>
			<text>This field can be used to record the processes used to collect
				the data in the dataset – for example, through experiments,
				interviews, or selection and digitization of print materials. It is
				also good practice to indicate any equipment used to generate the
				data, along with any relevant settings or parameters. (If not
				applicable, enter N/A.)
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_DatabaseDescription</helpId>
			<title>Database description</title>
			<text>This field should be used to describe the content and scope of
				the database, to record who created or compiled the data (and for
				what purpose), to state when the data was collected or digitized,
				and to supply any other information that may be needed to permit
				proper interpretation of the data at a later date, such as whether
				the data has been edited or manipulated since collection.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_EstimatedSize</helpId>
			<title>Estimated database size</title>
			<text>This defines the total space that will be available to your
				project for hosting databases. Please be aware that if you intend to
				create more than one version of any given database within your
				project (i.e. a separate test copy or ‘milestone’ copy), this will
				create a duplicate of that database, thus increasing your total
				space usage. The 25 GB option should be ample for research databases
				that do not contain more than 100,000 records and do not include
				images, audio files, or other multimedia, even if you make two
				duplicates. If you are intending to build a database larger than
				this, or which contains multimedia, you may wish to consider the 100
				GB option. If you exceed your allotted space you will be asked if
				you would like to switch to a larger allowance, but this will entail
				moving to a different pricing plan. The ORDS is not designed to cope
				with very large databases although if you think you might require
				more than 100 GB we may be able to create a customized virtual
				machine that will suit your requirement. Please email us if that is
				the case.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_WebAppName</helpId>
			<title>Database interface name</title>
			<text>This text will form part of the URL where your database can be
				accessed online. It must consist only of alphabetic and numeric
				characters, i.e. a..z, 0..9, and cannot contain spaces.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
	<helpGroup description="Login popup">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>LoginPopup_RememberMe</helpId>
			<title>Remember me</title>
			<text>Only select this option if you are the only person using this
				computer.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
	<helpGroup description="Project Creation popup">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_StartDate</helpId>
			<title>Start Date</title>
			<text>James to write this
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_EndDate</helpId>
			<title>End Date</title>
			<text>James to write this
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_SpaceAllocation</helpId>
			<title>Project space allocation</title>
			<text>This defines the total space that will be available to your
				project for hosting databases. Please be aware that if you intend to
				create more than one version of any given database within your
				project (i.e. a separate test copy or 'milestone' copy), this will
				create a duplicate of that database, thus increasing your total
				space usage. The 25 GB option should be ample for research databases
				that do not contain more than 100,000 records and do not include
				images, audio files, or other multimedia, even if you make two
				duplicates. If you are intending to build a database larger than
				this, or which contains multimedia, you may wish to consider the 100
				GB option. If you exceed your allotted space you will be asked if
				you would like to switch to a larger allowance, but this will entail
				moving to a different pricing plan. The ORDS is not designed to cope
				with very large databases although if you think you might require
				more than 100 GB we may be able to create a customized virtual
				machine that will suit your requirement. Please email us if that is
				the case.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_StorageType</helpId>
			<title>Project storage type</title>
			<text>Choosing the 'private cloud' option will ensure that your data
				remains within Oxford University. For some projects this may be
				necessary to meet the requirements of confidentiality or licensing
				agreements. If these issues are not relevant to your project, then
				allowing your data to be stored in the public cloud may be a less
				expensive option.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_AddPayment</helpId>
			<title>Add payment</title>
			<text>If you know how payment for your use of ORDS will be made you
				can add a payment method, eg a journal transfer, invoice etc.
				However, you do not need to add a payment method at this stage.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_Description</helpId>
			<title>Description</title>
			<text>This description will appear on your ORDS project list page. It
				will be visible to everyone who is a member of the project, and will
				act as a summary of what the project is about. This field can be
				used to describe the subject matter and scope of the project, and to
				supply other relevant information such as details of the people
				involved, or the URL of a project website.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
	<helpGroup description="Add new members to project popup">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>AddNewMembersPopup_Email</helpId>
			<title>Email</title>
			<text>This needs to be the email of the user you wish to join your
				project that they have used to register with ORDS.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>AddNewMembersPopup_Role</helpId>
			<title>Role</title>
			<text>Project members will have one of the following roles:
				Project
				Administrator; Contributor; Viewer. Additionally, the person who
				initiated the project will automatically inherit the role of Project
				Owner.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
</helpText>