<helpText language="En_US">
	<helpGroup
		description="Fields shown when a user creates a new database (aka'dataspace') within a project">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_DatabaseName</helpId>
			<title>Database Name</title>
			<text>The database name you choose can only contain alphabetic and
				numeric characters, i.e. a..z, 0..9, and cannot contain spaces.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_EstimatedSize</helpId>
			<title>Estimated Database Size</title>
			<text>This defines the total space that will be available to your
				project for hosting databases. Please be aware that if you intend to
				create more than one version of any given database within your
				project (i.e. a separate test copy or ‘milestone’ copy), this will
				create a duplicate of that database, thus increasing your total
				space usage. The 25 GB option should be ample for research databases
				that do not contain more than 100,000 records and do not include
				images, audio files, or other multimedia, even if you make two
				duplicates. If you are intending to build a database larger than
				this, or which contains multimedia, you may wish to consider the 100
				GB option. If you exceed your allotted space you will be asked if
				you would like to switch to a larger allowance, but this will entail
				moving to a different pricing plan. The ORDS is not designed to cope
				with very large databases although if you think you might require
				more than 100 GB we may be able to create a customized virtual
				machine that will suit your requirement. Please email us if that is
				the case.</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>DatabaseCreationPopup_WebAppName</helpId>
			<title>Database interface name</title>
			<text>This text will form part of the URL where your database can be
				accessed online. It must consist only of alphabetic and numeric
				characters, i.e. a..z, 0..9, and cannot contain spaces.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
	<helpGroup description="Login popup">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>LoginPopup_RememberMe</helpId>
			<title>Remember me</title>
			<text>Only select this option if you are the only person using this
				computer.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
	<helpGroup description="Project Creation popup">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_StartDate</helpId>
			<title>Start Date</title>
			<text>James to write this
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
		<helpField>
			<helpId>ProjectCreationPopup_EndDate</helpId>
			<title>End Date</title>
			<text>James to write this
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
	<helpGroup description="Add new members to project popup">
		<helpField>
			<helpId>AddNewMembersPopup_Role</helpId>
			<title>Role</title>
			<text>Project members will have one of the following roles:
				Project
				Administrator; Contributor; Viewer. Additionally, the person who
				initiated the project will automatically inherit the role of Project
				Owner.
			</text>
			<image>help</image>
		</helpField>
	</helpGroup>
</helpText>